
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="article_title">DuckDuckGo</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">#Positive replies to your queries</string>
    <string name="article_text">Google is notoriously hard to get a hold of. Locked out of your Gmail account? Sorry, we can’t help you. The Knowledge Graph says you’re dead? That’s unfortunate. Unless you’re a journalist or influencer of some kind, good luck getting anyone at Google to listen.
\n\n

<b># DuckDuckGo doesn’t try to trap you in their “ecosystem.”</b>
\n\n
<b><i>#Search without fear.
</i></b> -When we know that we’re being watched , definitely there will be change in our behaviour.It’s  well documented behaviour called the chilling effect, and it happens when we know that somebody is tracking us.For example,  an MIT study showed that people started doing fewer health searches on Google after the Snowden revelations, fearing that their personal ailments might get out.


\n\n
<b><i></i></b> and <b><i></i></b> —Definitely we  can’t compare DuckDuckGo with Google because Google is giant with 75,000 employees ,dominating search, online advertising , browsing, etc. While DuckDuckGo , According to 2017 statistics, they’re team of about 45 people scattered across globe
<b><i></i></b> — When it comes to platforms such as Android and iOS, DuckDuckGo makes sure that It goes the extra mile to protect user privacy.
So instead of simply injecting its privacy tools into various other Android apps, it gives users the option of replacing their current web browser pretty much wholesale with DuckDuckGo’s Privacy Browser app.

\n\n
<b><i>Love Me Do</i></b> —  In fact , in many respects , DuckDuckGo is better .It’s search aren’t littered with Google Products and services - boxes and carousels to try and persuade people to spend more time in Google’s family of apps.

\n\n
<b><i></i></b> —Search for, say, ‘Avengers’ and Google will first tell you it can be purchased from Google Play or YouTube with the price of  Rs 50. It will then suggest you play a trailer for the film on, where else, YouTube. The film is also “liked” by 92 per cent of Google users and people searching for this also search for, you guessed it, Avengers end game and Marvel’s Avengers. The same search on DuckDuckGo pulls in a snippet from Wikipedia and quick links to find out more on IMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Amazon ,etc. For the most part, the top of Google’s page of results directs us more towards the Google products and services.Go further and search for ‘Avengers cast’ and Google displays a carousel of names and pictures right at the top of the page
<b><i></i></b> —slapping it with multi-billion pound fines and launching investigation after investigation into alleged anti-competitive behaviour. What’s good for Google, the commission argues, isn’t necessarily good for consumers or competitors.
\n\n
<b><i>One After 909</i></b> — As a result, 50 per cent of all Google searches now end without a click. Great for Google, bad for the list of websites below that also contain this information and that you will never visit. Do the same search on DuckDuckGo and the top result is IMDb. It might sound small but issues like this are fundamental to how the internet works – and who makes the most money from it. Google’s prioritisation of its results, and a perceived bias towards its own products and services, has landed the company in hot water with the European Commission
</string>
</resources>